bubblicious.com 2014-12-19

# Mondelēz International, Inc. Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: October 28, 2014**

  * Scope
  * Information We Collect
  * Your Control of Cookies
  * How We Use Your Information
  * How We Share Your Information
  * How We Protect Your Information
  * Choice & Control
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * Children's Privacy
  * Other Information
  * Changes to Our Privacy Statement
  * Contact Us

### Scope 

This privacy statement applies to MondelezInternational.com and Mondelēz Global LLC ("Mondelēz Global ") websites, services, applications and products that collect data and display these terms (collectively, our "sites"). It does not apply to Mondelēz Global sites, services and products that do not display or link to this statement or that have their own privacy statements.

### Information We Collect 

#### more info

Mondelēz Global collects many types of information in order to operate effectively and provide you the best products, services and experiences we can. This information includes:

  * Information you provide (for example, when you register with our sites, sign up for our newsletters or email lists, participate in surveys and purchase our products or services);
  * Information collected automatically (for example, we may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies that collect non-personal information about your use of our sites, interactions with our emails, and information about your computer and web browser);
  * Information collected from other sources (for example, we may collect information from commercially available sources such as data aggregators and public databases).

We may also combine this information to help us tailor our communications and advertisements to you, develop exceptional products and services, and improve our sites. Information Collected Automatically by Our Partners

  * We also use third party ad networks and similar providers to serve advertisements on our sites. These providers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect non-personal information such as your IP address. They may also use anonymous data received from third parties to assist them in delivering more meaningful advertisements to you.

### Your Ability to Control Cookies and Similar Technologies 

#### more info

Cookies, web beacons, Flash cookies and similar technologies serve many important functions that help us serve you better. However, you have a variety of tools to control cookies and similar technologies, including:

  * Web browser controls to block and delete cookies, or adjust your tracking preferences;
  * Visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance's opt-out page [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies;
  * Information on how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager06.html).

### How We Use Your Personal Information 

#### more info

Mondelēz Global uses the information we collect for many important purposes, including to:

  * Provide the products and services you request;
  * Communicate with you regarding our products and services, as well as those of our partners and affiliates; 
  * Share or post reviews of our products and services; and
  * Display more meaningful and relevant advertisements.

### How We Share Your Personal Information 

#### more info

Mondelēz Global does not sell or disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent, except where:

  * We engage third-party service providers to assist us with the activities identified in this privacy statement. In these situations, we only allow these providers to use your personal information as necessary to perform activities on our behalf or to comply with a legal requirement;
  * We conduct joint promotions with other companies and sharing your personal information is necessary to conduct the promotion. We will not share your personal information with our promotional partners for any other reason;
  * It is necessary to prevent crime or injury, or as otherwise required by law; and
  * Another company acquires us or any of our assets.

### How We Protect Your Information 

#### more info

Mondelēz Global maintains administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect your personal information.

### Choice & Control Over Your Personal Information 

#### more info

To change how Mondelēz Global contacts you, to correct or change your information or to cancel your registration with us, you can either update your information in the Your Profile section of our sites or email our Online Team using the form found at the following [page](http://mdlz.custhelp.com/app/contact/sa/1/).

### Your California Privacy Rights 

#### more info

Mondelēz Global may share your personal information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the Mondelēz name, for their own direct marketing purposes. If you would like to learn more about the types of personal information we share and who we share it with, write to us at: Mondelēz Global LLC • 100 Deforest Avenue • East Hanover, NJ 07936 • Attention: Legal Department.

### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy 

#### more info

Mondelēz Global's sites are intended for general audiences and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our sites.

### Other Information 

#### more info

#### Links to Other Sites

  * Mondelēz Global tries to make sure that any links on our sites send you to a helpful and reliable place on the Internet, but we are not responsible for the content of these other sites or their privacy practices.

#### Public Forums & Reviews

  * You may use our sites to post reviews of our products and services, but once you do, it becomes public information and we may continue to display your content even if you terminate your account.

### Updates to Our Privacy Statement 

#### more info

Check this privacy statement from time to time, as we may change or update portions of this statement at any time and without prior notice to you.

### How to Contact Us 

#### more info

Mondelēz Global LLC • 100 Deforest Avenue • East Hanover, NJ 07936 • Attention: Legal Department

### Information We Collect

#### Information You Provide

At our sites, we collect information from you when you choose to share it with us to use our sites or services, register with our sites, sign up for newsletters or our e-mail list, sign up to receive text message alerts, participate in an online or text message survey or promotion, purchase products or services from us, or otherwise contact us. The information we collect may include your name, address, telephone number, mobile telephone number, e-mail address, age, gender, photo/image and, if you make a purchase on our sites, credit/debit card number or other financial information. You may also be required to provide certain information to create an online account. While some information is mandatory to create your account, you can control what information is available to other members on our sites. We do not require you to register or provide this information to us in order to view our sites or have access to most site content.

#### Information Collected Automatically

We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to and users of our sites to deliver online advertisements that we think would be more relevant to your interests, and to monitor interactions with our emails, text messages and online advertisements. For example, we may automatically collect certain non-personal information from you, such as the type of web browser and operating system you use, the name of your Internet Service Provider, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, software version, course geolocation information (for example, based on IP address or location of cellular tower used for the connection), and the domain name from which you accessed our sites. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit our sites, the areas or pages of our sites that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using our sites, the number of times you return to our sites, other click-stream or site usage data, emails or ads that you open, forward or click-through to our sites. Collecting this information, and linking it with your personally-identifiable information, helps us best tailor our sites and enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting our sites, and to help us identify sites features, advertisements, and offers that may be of particular interest to you.

#### Information Collected from Other Sources

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators and public databases. This information may include name, demographic information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and shopping behavior.

#### Combination of Information

We may combine the information we receive from and about you, including personal and non-personal information collected through our sites, to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our sites, services, and products.

#### Information Collected Automatically by Our Partners

We also may use third party advertisements placed by ad networks to support our sites. Some of these advertisers and ad networks may use technology such as cookies and web beacons/pixel tags when they advertise on our sites, which may send these advertisers and ad networks information including your non-personal information, such as your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our sites, and whether you have Flash installed. Some of these advertisers and ad networks also may use anonymous data, such as demographic data, received from third parties to assist in the delivery of advertisements to you. These advertisers and ad networks use the information described above to provide you relevant advertisements based on your online behavior, search activities on our site and on other third party sites, and demographic information relevant to your general location, so that the advertising you see on our sites more closely reflects your interests and needs.

### Your Ability to Control Cookies and Similar Technologies

You can set your Internet browser or operating system settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, to omit images (which will disable pixel tags) or adjust your tracking preferences. Note that the opt-out will apply only to the browser that you are using when you elect to opt out of advertising cookies. You can opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance's opt-out page [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager06.html). Without cookies or pixel tags though, you may not be able to take full advantage of our sites' features. Check the "Tools" or "Help" tab on your browser to learn how to change your cookie and other tracking preferences. Note, however, that our systems may not recognize Do Not Track (DNT) headers from some or all browsers.

### How We Use Your Personal Information

Mondelēz Global may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:

  * To respond to your questions or comments, fulfill orders, process payments and prevent transactional fraud, provide services, and contact and communicate with you;
  * To provide you with customized sites content, targeted offers, and advertising on our sites, on other sites, or via email or text message;
  * To contact you with information, newsletters, and promotional materials from Mondelēz Global or on behalf of our partners and affiliates;
  * To post review of products and services on our sites;
  * To develop new products or services;
  * To address problems and review the usage and operations of our sites or business and improve our content, products, and services;
  * To manage our telecommunications networks;
  * To protect the security or integrity of our sites and our business; and
  * As described to you at the point of data collection. 

### How We Share Your Personal Information

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personally-identifiable information about our sites' visitors, except as described here. We do not share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent. For California residents, please see "Your California Privacy Rights" below.

We may share personally identifiable information among Mondelēz Global brands, affiliates and subsidiaries. In the course of doing business, we employ other companies and individuals to perform a variety of functions on our behalf. For example, we hire agencies to help administer consumer promotions, to analyze data, to fulfill orders you place, and to provide customer service. These service providers may have access to personally identifiable information about our website visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for Mondelēz Global, but they are not authorized by Mondelēz Global to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on Mondelēz Global's behalf or to comply with legal requirements, and they are required to maintain the information in confidence. In addition, we may disclose information where we think it's necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, if required by law, or in response to a request from law enforcement authorities or other government officials.

We may conduct joint promotions with other companies. We may share with our promotional partners (and their service providers) certain personally-identifiable information as necessary to conduct the promotion. We will not share this information with our promotional partners for any other purpose unless you consent to such sharing.

During the normal course of our business, Mondelēz Global may sell or purchase assets or equity. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personally identifiable information provided through this website in a manner that is consistent with this privacy statement.

### How We Protect Your Information

Protecting your personal information is important to us. We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help protect against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the personally identifiable information we collect on our sites.

### Choice & Control Over Your Personal Information

You are ultimately in control of the personal information you provide to us on our sites. For example, you can change your preference for follow-up contacts by e-mailing the Online Team at the address found at the paged linked to below or by changing the information in the Your Profile (or similar) section of our sites. If you prefer, you can cancel your registration and we will take steps to remove your personal information from our database. E-mail the Online team using the form at the page linked to below if you wish to take this action: [Consumer Response Email](http://mdlz.custhelp.com/app/contact/sa/1/)

### Your California Privacy Rights

For California Residents Only. We may share your personally-identifiable information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the Mondelēz Global name, for their own direct marketing purposes. If you would like to learn more about the types of personal information we share with these affiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes, or their identities, please send a letter with your name, postal address, and e-mail, with the heading "California Privacy Rights" to: 

Mondelēz Global LLC • 100 Deforest Avenue • East Hanover, NJ 07936 • Attention: Legal Department

### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Our sites are intended for general audiences and Mondelēz Global does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our sites. We might permit a child to send us an e-mail. We will respond to or deliver these e-mails, but we do not store the names, e-mail addresses, or the e-mails themselves in our operational database. We do not maintain this information, nor do we share it with third parties (other than support service companies as described above).

Under federal law, websites directed to children under 13 are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to engage in the activity. We comply fully with this requirement.

Upon proper identification, any parent can review any personal information we have collected from their child, if we are still maintaining the information in our operational database. They may also request that the information be deleted from our database, and refuse to permit further collection or use of their child's information. If you are a parent and wish to exercise these rights, please contact the Online Team as described below.

### Other Information

#### Links to Other Sites

Mondelēz Global reasonably tries to make sure that every link on our sites sends you to a helpful place on the Internet. We provide these links solely for your convenience and information. In addition, different websites have different privacy statements associated with the use of those sites. Please check the privacy statement of the specific site you're visiting to understand the privacy practices associated with that site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party websites.

#### Public Forums & Reviews

You may use our sites to post reviews of products and services. Any information, such as reviews, that you may disclose to your network of connections on our sites, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on our sites, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. If you terminate your account, we may continue to show some of your content in anonymized form.

### Updates to Our Privacy Statement

We may change or update portions of this privacy statement at any time and without prior notice to you. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the privacy statement. We will indicate the privacy statement's effective date on the first page of the privacy statement.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about our privacy statement or practices, you can contact us at:

Mondelēz Global LLC • 100 Deforest Avenue • East Hanover, NJ 07936 • Attention: Legal Department

We'll be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
